# TAN NGUYEN LE

Phone: 0467580942 Address Email: nguyenletan@gmail.com Noble Park, Victoria, Australia

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/nguyenletan/">https://github.com/nguyenletan/</a> My website: <a href="https://tannguyenle.info">https://tannguyenle.info</a>

Front-end developer with experience in building webapps based on React.js, GatsbyJs and Pure HTML + CSS + JavaScript/Typescript. I also know Angular, VueJs, jQuery. I have over 10 years in software development. Back-end development enthusiast with knowledge of .NET, NodeJS, GraphQL PostgreSQL, MS-SQL, and MySQL. Love to experiment with new technologies, promote & help beginners getting comfortable with Open Source.

# **EDUCATION**

**BS** University of Science - Ho Chi Minh City - Vietnam

Feb 2006

Software Engineering

Graduated with a CGPA of 8.02 / 10 (UGC 10-point system)

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

More 10 years' experience in Software Engineering and Web development.

**Programming**: JavaScript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, C#.

Framework / Library: ReactJS, Gatsby, Nextjs, Bootstrap, Vuejs, Angular, jQuery

Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MS-SQL

**OS**: Windows, MACOS

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

BEE (Singapore Startup) Sep 2020 - Now

Full stack NodeJS developer

Our Very Own, Australia Jan 2021 to Jun 2021

Front End developer

NashTech, Vietnam Dec 2009 to Jan 2020

Senior Front End Software Engineer

Pyramid Consulting, Vietnam 2007 to 2009

.NET Software engineer

#### **PROJECTS**

# **BEE** (Singapore startup)

Sep 2020 to Now

- BEE acts as a dedicated Business Intelligence (BI) software that provides visibility to client organisations on electrical energy performance estimates from their facility's (building's) electrical consumption.
- Use Postgres database, ReactJs and Recoil for front-end side, NestJs + Prisma Js for API back-end side.
- Use React, Gatsby, Bootstrap and Drupal to implement
- Tech stack: ReactJS, Bootstrap, Styled Component, NestJs, NodeJs, Prisma.

KidsFirst Jan 2021 to Jun 2021

- Website: <a href="https://www.kidsfirstaustralia.org.au/">https://www.kidsfirstaustralia.org.au/</a>
- Kids First is a leading provider of education, family, and support services for children and families in Melbourne. Kids First have over 120 years in the childcare industry. In 2019, Kids First revamped its website to give it a new, professional, and modern look. They also wanted to improve its speed by using GatsbyJs an open-source static website generator (SSG).
- Use React, Gatsby, Bootstrap and Drupal to implement
- Tech stack: ReactJS, GatsbyJs, Bootstrap, Styled Component

# **Personal website**, side project

June 2020 to July 2020

- Website: <a href="https://tannguyenle.info">https://tannguyenle.info</a>
- GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/nguyenletan/porfolio">https://github.com/nguyenletan/porfolio</a>
- Use React, Gatsby and ThemeUI to implement
- Tech stack: ReactJS, GatsbyJs, ThemeUI, Styled Component

# August Demo, side project

27 July 2020

- Website: <a href="https://august-demo.netlify.app">https://august-demo.netlify.app</a>
- GitHub: https://github.com/nguyenletan/august
- This is my side project. I tried to copy this August home page to show my skill.
- Use React, Bootstrap and Styled Component to implement
- Tech stack: ReactJS, GatsbyJs, Bootstrap, Styled Component

# PTE 79 Tips, side project

April 2020 to July 2020

- Website: https://pte79.tips
- GitHub: https://github.com/pte79/pte2
- This is my side project.

- Use React, Gatbsby and ThemeUI to implement
- PTE 79 Tips is bank of real exam questions on the market.
- Tech stack: ReactJS, GatsbyJs, ThemeUI, Styled Component

**Edvisor.io** Feb 2019 to Jan 2020

- Website: https://www.edvisor.io/
- Edvisor for Schools is a platform that helps schools push their offerings faster and further around the globe by providing a direct distribution channel to education consultants.
- implemented enrollment feature and fixing some legacy UI bugs.
- Tech stack: AngularJS 1.xx, GraphQL, NodeJs.

Pokémon Wiki Dec 2018 to July 2020

- Website: <a href="https://pokefor.dev/">https://pokefor.dev/</a>
- GitHub:
  - Front-end: https://github.com/nguyenletan/pokemon-wiki-react
  - Back-end: <a href="https://github.com/nguyenletan/pokemon-wiki-apollo">https://github.com/nguyenletan/pokemon-wiki-apollo</a>
- This is my side project.
- Use ReactJS and Apollo GraphQL to implement this site.
- Built a crowd sourced meta-Pokedex! We use GraphQL like a API Gateway to get data from the world's largest Pokémon GO database GO Hub's Pokémon GO.
- Tech stack: React.js, Apollo GraphQL.

iVisas Dec 2018 to July 2020

- GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/nguyenletan/IVisas">https://github.com/nguyenletan/IVisas</a>
- iVisas is a demo projects for a verifiable claim is qualification, achievement, quality, or piece of information about an entity's background such as a name, government ID, payment provider, home address, or university degree.
- Implemented all UI screens
- Tech stack: VueJs, Vuesax, NodesJs, PostgreSQL.

Cx Housing Dec 2011 to Dec 2016

- iVisas is a demo projects for a verifiable claim is qualification, achievement, quality, or piece of information about an entity's background such as a name, government ID, payment provider, home address, or university degree.
- Implemented all UI screens
- Tech stack: ASP.NET MVC, jQuery, KendoUI, MS-SQL

Vielife Jan 2010 to Oct 2011

- Vielife is a platform that provides personalised information on how to improve performance by focusing on sleep patterns and habits, stress management, nutrition and physical activity.
- Collaborated with cross-functional agile team of software engineers on the development, deployment, and troubleshooting various legacy bugs.
- Tech stack: ASP.NET MVC, ¡Query, KendoUI, MS-SQL.

# Marqui CMS

May 2006 to May 2007

- Marqui CMS is a web content management platform serving small marketing teams
  to large multi-site organizations with various pages and users.
   Collaborated with cross-functional agile team of software engineers on the
  development, deployment, and troubleshooting various legacy bugs.
- Used ASP.NET Webform HTML, CSS, and jQuery to build friendly UIs.
- Tech stack: ASP.NET Webform, jQuery, MS-SQL.

#### REFERENCES

# Huy Nguyen, Principle Engineer

Atlassian, Sydney, Australia

Phone: 0403981380

Email: tuonghuy@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/huy-nguyen-073a9023">https://www.linkedin.com/in/huy-nguyen-073a9023</a>

# Phi Huynh, Senior Innovation Manager

NashTech Limited, Vietnam

Phone: +84919833383

Email: phi.huynh@nashtechglobal.com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/trumhemcut/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/trumhemcut/</a>

### Toan Vo

Senior Developer MYOB, New Zealand Phone: +642108774618

Email: toan.vo@myob.com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/toanvo/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/toanvo/</a>

# **Cuong Le**

Senior Developer

Rosslyn Data Technologies, London, UK

Phone: +07719240314

Email: cuong.le@rosslyndatatech.com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/cuongln/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/cuongln/</a>